Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- Thomas Jefferson to Peter Freneau, 1803 May 20; No. 642
- Thomas Jefferson to Don Bernardo de Galvez, 1780 January 29; No. 643
- Thomas Jefferson to Elbridge Gerry, 1786 May 7; No. 644
- Thomas Jefferson to Rev. Frederick W. Hatch, 1821 December 8; No. 645
- Thomas Jefferson to William Hilliard, 1826 May 6; No. 646; Requests that Hilliard send specified books.
  David Library Item Number: 646; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to the Governor of Connecticut (Samuel Huntington), 1790 August 18; No. 647
- Thomas Jefferson to William Hylton, 1801 June 5; No. 648
- Thomas Jefferson to the inhabitants of the town of Orland, Me., 1808 September-October; No. 649
- Thomas Jefferson to James Maury, 1787 November 13; No. 650
- Thomas Jefferson to James Maury, 1791 August 30; No. 651
- Thomas Jefferson to William D. Meriwether, 1816 October 30; No. 652; Expresses willingness to relinquish possession of property that Jefferson bought from the guardians of the children of Bennet Henderson and to pay any rents legally due thereon.
  David Library Item Number: 652; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Jacques Necker, 1789 January 24; No. 653
- Thomas Jefferson to Richard "O'Brien" O'Bryen, 1785 September 29; No. 654
- Thomas Jefferson to James Oldham, 1803 November 28; No. 655
- Thomas Jefferson to Charles Wilson Peale, 1806 January 24; No. 656
- Thomas Jefferson to Thomas Mann Randolph, 1803 June 3; No. 657
- Thomas Jefferson to Joseph Rapin, 1802 June 3; No. 658
- Thomas Jefferson to George Read, Jr., 1790 August 12; No. 659
- Thomas Jefferson to Henry Remsen, Jr., 1791 November 14; No. 660
- Thomas Jefferson to Spencer Roane, 1819 September 6; No. 661; Argues that the revolution of 1800 was as much a real revolution in the principles of government as that of 1776 was a revolution in the form of government; comments on the separation of powers in government, the sedition law, Marbury vs. Madison, and other events that occurred during Jefferson's administration; remarks that Jefferson withdraws from all contests of opinion and defers to the new generation that is wiser because of "the progressive advance of science."
  David Library Item Number: 661; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Spencer Roane, 1821 June 27; No. 662; Informs Roane that Jefferson will make an exception and recommend a book to the public. Contains extract of another letter from Jefferson pertaining to the same book.
  David Library Item Number: 662; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to William Short, 1800 March 26; No. 663
- Thomas Jefferson to St. George Tucker, 1779 June 22; No. 664
- Thomas Jefferson to John Francis Vacher, 1804 March 23; No. 665
- Thomas Jefferson to John Vaughan, 1815 December 22; No. 666; Mentions that wines are being sent to Jefferson; requests that he purchase two specified books for Jefferson from [George] Ticknor's [auction] catalogue.
  David Library Item Number: 666; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to David Bailie Warden, 1808 July 16; No. 667
- Thomas Jefferson to Emma Hart Willard, 1819 December 18; No. 668; Thanks her for sending a copy of her book on female eduction and comments that "the subject is of great importance and of lamentable deficiency in this country."
  David Library Item Number: 668; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- Thomas Jefferson to Alexander Wilson, 1805 April 7; No. 669
- Thomas Jefferson to James Oldham, 1802 January 2; No. 670
- Thomas Jefferson to Thomas Walker Maury, 1826 March 3; No. 671
- Thomas Jefferson, 1803 July 12; No. 672
- Thomas Jefferson to John Barnes, 1802 April 26; No. 673
- Thomas Jefferson, and others, No. 674; List of subscribers, including Thomas Jefferson, who promise to pay specified sums for equipping a volunteer company from Albemarle County, [Va] that will offer its services to the President of the United States for one year.
  David Library Item Number: 674; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- David Jeffries to David D. Rogers, 1780 June 23; No. 675
- David Jeffries to Joseph P. Palmer, 1780 June 27; No. 676
- David Jeffries to William and John Molineux, 1779 June 2; No. 677
- Daniel Jenifer of St. Thomas to Charles Lee, 1776 July 17; No. 678
- Francis Johnston to Thomas Mifflin, 1790 July 2; No. 679
- George Johnston, on behalf of George Washington, 1777 March 29; No. 680
- Samuel Johnston to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 29; No. 681
- Gabriel Johonnat to Joshua Loring, 1780 December 8; No. 682
- Gabriel Jones to James Wood, 1782 December 20; No. 683
- Nicholas Jones, 1776-1783; No. 684
- Johann baron de Kalb to Richard Caswell, 1780 June 16; No. 685
- Dr. John Kemp to Tench Coxe, 1791 December 25; No. 686
- Thomas Kempton, 1775 August 1; No. 687
  Missing since 8/2006.
- Ebenezer Kent to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 15; No. 688
- Augustus Keppel to Joshua Sharpe, 1779 July 29; No. 689
- P.G. Kerveguen to Baron Claude Dallemagne, 1794 June 6; No. 690
- Rufus King to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard, and McEvers, 1813 July 1; No. 691
- Peter Kinnan to Michael Vreeland, 1780 September 16; No. 692
- Frederick Kitt to Bartholomew Dandridge, 1795 March 23, 1796 October 3; No. 693
- Julius Klingsohr to George Yonge, 1787 October 26; No. 694
- James Knowles to his wife, 1776 January 15; No. 695
- Regarding Henry Knox, 1806?; No. 696
- Henry Knox to Ralph H. Bowles, 1790 September 29; No. 697
- Henry Knox to John Cochran, 1792 August 13; No. 698
- Henry Knox to John Gleason, 1804 April 10; No. 699
- Henry Knox to Samuel Hodgdon, 1794 February 11; No. 700
- Henry Knox to Samuel Hodgdon, 1797 October 25; No. 701
- Henry Knox to Henry Jackson, 1781 November 15; No. 702
- Henry Knox to William Knox, 1792 May 25; No. 703
- Henry Knox to the Secretary of War James McHenry, 1798 August 5; No. 704
- Henry Knox to Isaac Winslow, 1785 September 5; No. 705
- Henry Knox to ________, October 13; No. 706
- Robert Knox, 1781 December 4; No. 707
- Robert Knox to whom it may concern, 1781 December 27; No. 708
- Tadeusz Andrzej Bonawentura Kosciuszko to John Armstrong, December 13; No. 709
- Tadeusz Andrzej Bonawentura Kosciuszko to Nathanael Greene, 1782 December 26; No. 710
- Lajos Kossuth to Jacques-Alexander Bixio, 1859 May 7; No. 711
- German Record, 1776 December-1777 October; No. 712
- Allen Lackington and Company to Rufus King, on behalf of Oliver Ellsworth, 1801 March 21; No. 713
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to Francois-Jean Baudouin, 1818 November 15; No. 714
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. ______ Bazard, 1832 August 30; No. 715
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. ______ Charrolais, 1827 July 21; No. 716
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. ______ Charrolais, 1828 August 15; No. 717
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. _____ Fay, 1828 June 16; No. 718
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. _____ Fay, 1828 July 7; No. 719
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to General Camille-Alphonse Trezel?, 1840 February 15; No. 720
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to ________, 1826 March 29; No. 721
- George-Washington-Louis-Gilbert du Motier de Lafayette to M. ______ Honore, 1831 January 18; No. 722
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1778 March 14; No. 723
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1808 January 10; No. 724
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Sir Joseph Banks, n.d.; No. 725
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to George and Clara Baldwin, 1828 January 1; No. 726
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to James Fenimore Cooper, 1830 November; No. 727
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to William H. Crawford, 1824 May 14; No. 728
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Emeric-Joseph, duc de Dalberg, 1827 April 25; No. 729
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Issac Fletcher, 1825 August 13; No. 730
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Issac Fletcher, 1828 April 4; No. 731
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to the National Guard of Moulins-Engilbert, 1831 March 22; No. 732
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Alexander Hamilton, 1787 October 26; No. 733
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to M. ______ Hamilton, 1800(or later) November 6; No. 734
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Philip Hone, 1831 October 31; No. 735
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to M. _____ de Jouy, n.d.; No. 736
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard, and McEvers, 1815 March 5; No. 737
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to "Messieurs", 1789 July 18; No. 738
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to James Monroe, 1813 October 22; No. 739
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Sir Thomas Charles Morgan, 1816 August 18; No. 740
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Osgeanon-Don-Ha, 1786 January 17; No. 741
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Guglielmo Pepe, 1826 August 8; No. 742
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Guglielmo Pepe, 1828 May 3; No. 743
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Marie-Charles-Joseph de Pougens, 1800 December 11; No. 744
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Citizen Prochot, 1802 October 11; No. 745
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to M. _____ de Seelhorst, 1805 May 20; No. 746
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Aaron Vail, 1833 September 15; No. 747
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Martin Van Buren, 1830 December 28; No. 748
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to George Weedon, 1781 June 8; No. 749
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Marinus Willett, 1778 May 16; No. 750
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Jonathan Williams Jr., 1785 April 18; No. 751
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Jonathan Williams Jr., 1785 April 18; No. 752
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Samuel Williams, 1798 February 17; No. 753
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Samuel Williams, 1786 May 27; No. 754
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Jean-Paul Rabaut de St. Etienne, 1788 May 25; No. 755
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to Samuel Williams, 1824 December 11; No. 756
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to ________, January 11; No. 757
- Louis Giroux to ________, 1792 February 12; No. 758
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1789 September 15; No. 759
- Regarding Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette, 1825 June; No. 760
- Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de Lafayette to ________, 1830 November; No. 761
- Thomas Lamb to Henry Jackson, 1778 November 24; No. 762
- Thomas Lamb to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 16; No. 763
- John Langdon to Josiah Bartlett, 1778 June 20; No. 764
- Huson Langstroth, 1787 November 9; No. 765
- Philip Lansing to John Maley, 1775 January 28; No. 766
- Henry Laurens to Samuel Huntington, 1778 December 11; No. 767
- Henry Laurens to Don Diego Jose Navarro, 1778 October 27; No. 768
- Henry Laurens to George Read, 1778 February 10; No. 769
- John Laurens to Henry Laurens, 1775 November 24, December 5; No. 770
- William Lawrence, 1780 October 20; No. 771
- James Lawson, 1781 June 15; No. 772
- Tobias Lear to Alexander Macomb, 1790 February 4; No. 773
- Tobias Lear to George Washington, 1790 October 24; No. 774
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 March 31; No. 775
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 April 24; No. 776
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 May 22; No. 777
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 May 29; No. 778
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 June 5; No. 779
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 June 12; No. 780
- Tobias Lear to the President of the United States (George Washington), 1791 June 19; No. 781
- Tobias Lear to George Washington, 1793 November 3; No. 782
- Silvanus Learned to Andrew "Sigoney" Sigourney, 1782 March 14; No. 783
- Silvanus Learned to Andrew "Sigoney" Sigourney, 1782 May 24; No. 784
- Connecticut, Town of Lebanon, Selectman and Listers, 1778-1780; No. 785
- Charles Lee to James Bowdoin, 1776 November 21; No. 786
- Charles Lee to Zaccheus Collins, 1795 August 19; No. 787
- Charles Lee to Henry Lee, 1786 April 7; No. 788
- Charles Lee to Alexander McDougall, 1775 October 26; No. 789
- Charles Lee to Robert Morris or Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1777 February 9; No. 790
- Charles Lee to Dr. Benjamin Rush, 1776 November 2; No. 791
- Charles Lee to David Waterbury, "1775" 1776 January 16; No. 792
- Henry Lee to William Lee, 1793 January 21; No. 793
- Henry Lee to William Sullivan, 1797 May 31; No. 794
- Henry Lee to ________, n.d.; No. 795
- Henry Lee to Samuel Hughes, 1795 November 23; No. 796
- Richard Henry Lee to Dr. William Shippen, Jr., 1783 January 7; No. 797
- Richard Henry Lee to Charles Lee, 1776 July 6; No. 798
- Leffert Lefferts, 1793 August 4; No. 799
- Dominique L'Eglise to the Continental Congress, 1781 June 13; No. 800
- Solomon Leonard to Jacob Leonard, 1780 May 2; No. 801
- Solomon Leonard to Jacob Leonard, 1782 June 21; No. 802
- Solomon Leonard to Jacob Leonard, 1782 October 21; No. 803
- James McHenry to Thomas Sim Lee, 1781 June 19; No. 804
- ________ to the Lieutenant General Sir Jeffrey Amherst and the Principal Officers of His Majesty's Ordnance, 1778 September 10; No. 805
- John de Neufville to ________, 1779 July; No. 806
- Levy Andrew Levy to Joseph Bullock, 1780 March 10; No. 807
- Joseph Lewis, 1779 March-May; No. 808
- Morgan Lewis to ________, 1806 April 29; No. 809
- ________ Li Genevay to Jasper Yeates, 1776 April 1; No. 810
- Benjamin Lincoln to Matthew Clarkson, 1780 January 30; No. 811
- Benjamin Lincoln to Matthew Clarkson, 1781 May 3; No. 812
- Benjamin Lincoln to Matthew Clarkson, 1782 January 24; No. 813
- Benjamin Lincoln to William Woodford, 1780 March 8; No. 814
- Benjamin Lincoln to William Woodford, 1780 March 17; No. 815
- Charles Lining, 1779 September 27; No. 816
- Pendock Neal, 1781 April 9; No. 817
- Great Britain, Navy, 1777 February 8; No. 818
- Thomas Liston, Jr., 1779 June 20; No. 819
- William Little to Ebenezer Foote, 1779 August 22; No. 820
- James Livingston to Nathanael Greene, 1780 October 12; No. 821
- Philip Livingston to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard, and McEvers, 1805 November 28; No. 822
- Robert R. Livingston to the field officiers of Pennsylvania assembled at Lancaster, Pa., 1776 July 4; No. 823
- Robert R. Livingston to Gerard Bancker, 1783 August 1; No. 824
- Walter Livingston to Richard Varick, 1775 August 27; No. 825
- William Livingston, 1777 August 26; No. 826
- Isaac Longworth to Evert Bancker, 1762 September 20; No. 827
- Abraham Lott to William Livingston, 1782 June 9; No. 828
- United States Lottery, 1776 November 18; No. 829
- State of Pennsylvania Lottery, 1797 December 13; No. 830
- Louis XVI, King of France to Charles-Henri-Theodat, comte d'Estaing, 1782 October 20; No. 831
- Rev. David Love to the Lords Commissioners of His Majesty's Treasury, 1780 December 4; No. 832
- Rev. David Love to the General Assembly of Maryland, 1780? May; No. 833
- Anthony Low to ________, 1689 December 2; No. 834
- James Lovell to Samuel Holten, 1781 February 8; No. 835
- John Henry Lydius, John de Neufville, and Philip Hawkins, 1779 December 1; No. 836
- Andrew Lytle to Peter Gordon, 1780 March 23; No. 837
- John A. McAllister to Benson J. Lossing, 1855 May 18; No. 838
- George Macartney, 1768-1791; No. 839
- Malcolm McCourry, 1778 April 8; No. 840
- John McDonald to Philip Schuyler, 1776 April 22; No. 841
- Alexander McDougall to Aaron Burr, 1779 March 20; No. 842
- Alexander McDougall to George Washington, 1778 September 2; No. 843
- Alexander McDougall to Nathanael Greene, 1780 August 8; No. 844
- Alexander McDougall to William Hull, 1779 April 19; No. 845
- Alexander McDougall to John Lasher, 1779 April 3; No. 846
- James McHenry, 1779 September 11, 18, 19, 22, 23, October 2; No. 847
- James McHenry to Henry Knox, 1798 August 22; No. 848
- James McHenry to Henry Knox, 1798 August 22; No. 849
- James McHenry to Henry Knox, 1798 October 15; No. 850
- James McHenry to Jacob Read, 1784 December 5; No. 851
- James McHenry to George Washington, 1796 September 14; No. 852
- John McIntosh to Lachlan McIntosh, 1791 April 10; No. 853
- Lachlan McIntosh, 1789 January 1-1791 August 1; No. 854
- Lachlan McIntosh to Benjamin Lincoln, 1779 September 6; No. 855
- William MacKasson, 1775 August 27; No. 856
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Court, (Thomas McKean, Chief Justice) to the sheriffs or constables of Philadelphia, 1794 September 15; No. 857
- Thomas McKean, 1794 September 22; No. 858
- Thomas McKean, Notary Public, 1770 May 23; No. 859
- Thomas McKean to Caesar Rodney, 1778 April 20; No. 860
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Court, (Thomas McKean, Chief Justice) to the justices of the peace in Lancaster County, 1782 September 30; No. 861
- Robert McKenzie to Alexander Boyd, 1761 February 25; No. 862
- Robert MacKenzie, by order of Gen. Sir William Howe to all officers, soldiers, or followers of the army, 1776 December 24; No. 863
- John McKesson and Henry Merselis to Abraham Yates, Jr., 1793 September 18; No. 864
- Allan McLane to Captain ______ Hancock, 1819? July 5; No. 865
- Francis McLean to George Turner, 1780 May 17; No. 866
- James Madison to Dr. Thomas Cooper, 1826 December 26; No. 867
- James Madison to Thomas Jefferson, 1787 March 18; No. 868
- James Madison to Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette, 1828 August 21; No. 869
- James Madison to Philip Mazzei, 1788 October 8; No. 870
- James Madison to James Kirke Paulding, 1831 April; No. 871; Mentions the problems of writing biography and the deficiencies of oral tradition and comments briefly on [George] Washington, [Benjamin] Franklin, [Thomas] Jefferson, and John Adams and more extensively on [Alexander] Hamilton for Paulding's proposed "Biographical undertaking."
  David Library Item Number: 871; Description from Guide to the Sol Feinstone Collection of the David Library of the American Revolution.
- James Madison to Archibald Stuart, 1787 November 25; No. 872
- United States, President James Madison, 1809-1817; No. 873
- Regarding Chretien-Guillaume de Lamoignon de Malesherbes, No. 874
- Chretien-Guillaume de Lamoignon de Malesherbes to Arthur Lee, 1780 February 23; No. 875
- William Manson and Company, 1776 August 22-1780 January 5; No. 876; 1.0 vol.
- William Manson and Company, 1776 August 22-1780 January 5; No. 877; 1.0 vol.
- To the Manufacturers and Mechanics of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, the Northern Liberties, and District of Southwark, 1774 June 8; No. 878
- Henry Marble to Luke Drury, 1782 January 22; No. 879
- Massachusetts, Marblehead, Committee of Corrspondence to the Committee of Corrspondence or Selectmen of Haverhill, 1774 August 16; No. 880
- Elihu Marshall "to the Deranged Officers met at Mr. Hendrickson's", 1783 April 18; No. 881
- John Marshall to Elbridge Gerry, 1800 September 15; No. 882
- William Martin to Leonard Forrester, 1745 October 14; No. 883
- Elihu? Marvin to ________, 1776 February 26; No. 884
- State of Maryland, Court of Admiralty to Benjamin Nicholson, 1778 January 14; No. 885
- Richard Mason and Elizabeth Mason to Hugh Thompson, 1786 August 22; No. 886
- Province of Massachusetts Bay to Jonathan Simpson, 1771 July 20; No. 887
- Colony of Massachusetts Bay Congress to James Brickett, 1775 May 19; No. 888
- Colony of Massachusetts Bay Congress to Zaccheus Crocker, 1775 May 19; No. 889
- Colony of Massachusetts Bay Council to William Foster, 1776 May 10; No. 890
- Colony of Massachusetts Bay Council to George Godfrey, 1776 May 3; No. 891
- Colony of Massachusetts House of Representatives, 1776 January 17; No. 892
- Massachusetts, Town of Haverhill, 1779 October 15; No. 893
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Lieutenant Governor Samuel Adams, 1794 February 19; No. 894
- State of Massachusetts Bay to ________, 1777; No. 895
- State of Massachusetts Bay, Treasurer Henry Gardner to Samuel Dexter, 1777 July 17; No. 896
- State of Massachusetts Bay, Treasurer Henry Gardner to John White, 1777 December 1; No. 897
- William Davis, 1777 August 22; No. 898
- State of Massachusetts Bay Council, 1778 October 20; No. 899
- State of Massachusetts Bay Council to Henry Gardner, treasurer, 1777 July 30; No. 900
- State of Massachusetts Bay Council to Henry Gardner, treasurer, 1777 November 26; No. 901
- Artemus Ward, Jr., 1831 February 8; No. 902
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor John Hancock to Thomas Ivers, treasurer, 1783 March 26; No. 903
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor John Hancock, 1780 November 8; No. 904
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor Samuel Adams to Francis Jenks, 1794 July 24; No. 905
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor Samuel Adams to Sylvester Procter, 1795 October 22; No. 906
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Governor Samuel Adams to Winthrop Sargent, 1794 May 6; No. 907
- Colony of Massachusetts House of Representatives, 1776 January 4; No. 908
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts House of Representatives and Senate, 1786 November 17; No. 909
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Suffolk County Court, 1828 January 14-1831 February 8; No. 910
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Suffolk County Probate Office to Richard Cranch, 1789 January 16; No. 911
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts Supreme Court, 1788 April 14; No. 912
- Commonwealth of Massachusetts Supreme Court, 1790 April 13; No. 913
- State of Massachusetts Bay, Treasurer Henry Gardner to Timothy Hartshorne, 1780 June 25; No. 914
- Gabriel Maturin to Thomas Barrow, 1773 June 9; No. 915
- Rev. James Maury to Rev. William Douglass, 1758 May 31; No. 916
- Rev. James Maury to Rev. William Douglass, 1759 October 25; No. 917
- Rev. James Maury to Rev. William Douglass, 1759 November 20; No. 918
- Rev. James Maury to Moses Fontaine, 1755 August 9; No. 919
- Rev. James Maury to Moses Fontaine, 1756 June 10; No. 920
- Rev. James Maury to Moses Fontaine, 1759 June 11; No. 921
- Rev. James Maury to Moses Fontaine, 1756 February; No. 922